[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "Marc Lamont Hill, this guy is just a bigot, Ben, isn't he?", "question_tokens": ["Marc", "Lamont", "Hill", ",", "this", "guy", "is", "just", "a", "bigot", ",", "Ben", ",", "is", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "It's absolutely clear that he is a bigot and this isn't the case of him listing 11 sins and gay just happened to be on the list.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "absolutely", "clear", "that", "he", "is", "a", "bigot", "and", "this", "is", "n't", "the", "case", "of", "him", "listing", "11", "sins", "and", "gay", "just", "happened", "to", "be", "on", "the", "list", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marc Lamont Hill", "Ben"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Pennsylvania"]}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "MD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "What is your view on this, sir?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "on", "this", ",", "sir", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "First, he did express things in a rather crude way but would you got very upset about quoting from his message in Pennsylvania.", "answer_tokens": ["First", ",", "he", "did", "express", "things", "in", "a", "rather", "crude", "way", "but", "would", "you", "got", "very", "upset", "about", "quoting", "from", "his", "message", "in", "Pennsylvania", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "WRB", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "Are you sure about that?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "sure", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "If you let me finish, I'll tell you how.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "you", "let", "me", "finish", ",", "I", "'ll", "tell", "you", "how", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "This guy needs to go much 12 years of slave, doesn't he, Marc Lamont Hill?", "question_tokens": ["This", "guy", "needs", "to", "go", "much", "12", "years", "of", "slave", ",", "does", "n't", "he", ",", "Marc", "Lamont", "Hill", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "Or just have a common sense.", "answer_tokens": ["Or", "just", "have", "a", "common", "sense", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marc Lamont"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Today"]}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 218, "question": "Which one?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 219, "answer": "ERGUSON: Today, I want to say that this is my problem with this.", "answer_tokens": ["ERGUSON", ":", "Today", ",", "I", "want", "to", "say", "that", "this", "is", "my", "problem", "with", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "... he gets booted off and then how can it possibly be?", "question_tokens": ["...", "he", "gets", "booted", "off", "and", "then", "how", "can", "it", "possibly", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "CC", "RB", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "Wait a minute.", "answer_tokens": ["Wait", "a", "minute", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "Now, wait a minute, are you saying gay?", "question_tokens": ["Now", ",", "wait", "a", "minute", ",", "are", "you", "saying", "gay", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "Let me tell you -- let me finish.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "tell", "you", "--", "let", "me", "finish", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "PRP", "CD", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "Why should you Dr. Michael Brown be entitled to more rights in America than somebody who's gay?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "should", "you", "Dr.", "Michael", "Brown", "be", "entitled", "to", "more", "rights", "in", "America", "than", "somebody", "who", "'s", "gay", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "RBR", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "Give me one who had the right to marry three women.", "answer_tokens": ["Give", "me", "one", "who", "had", "the", "right", "to", "marry", "three", "women", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dr. Michael Brown"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 273, "question": "Piers Morgan, should he have that right, sir?", "question_tokens": ["Piers", "Morgan", ",", "should", "he", "have", "that", "right", ",", "sir", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "RB", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "You personally would like to have more rights than a ...", "answer_tokens": ["You", "personally", "would", "like", "to", "have", "more", "rights", "than", "a", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "... in America?", "question_tokens": ["...", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "Marriage is union of man and a woman.", "answer_tokens": ["Marriage", "is", "union", "of", "man", "and", "a", "woman", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "That's not -- what's the question I asked you?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "not", "--", "what", "'s", "the", "question", "I", "asked", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "... benefits on that.", "answer_tokens": ["...", "benefits", "on", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "Yes or no?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", "or", "no", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "No, of course not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "of", "course", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 297, "question": "So should two brothers deal out to marry?", "question_tokens": ["So", "should", "two", "brothers", "deal", "out", "to", "marry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "MD", "CD", "NNS", "VBP", "RP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 298, "answer": "Let me -- OK.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "--", "OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dr. Brown"]}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "There are cases in court about this?", "question_tokens": ["There", "are", "cases", "in", "court", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "You're getting silly, Dr. Brown.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'re", "getting", "silly", ",", "Dr.", "Brown", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 309, "question": "Why is that ridiculous?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "that", "ridiculous", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "This is what happens...", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "what", "happens", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 332, "question": "Courageous?", "question_tokens": ["Courageous", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "I'm not sure...", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "sure", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "Marc Lamont Hill?", "question_tokens": ["Marc", "Lamont", "Hill", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "I'm not sure it's courageous.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "sure", "it", "'s", "courageous", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marc Lamont"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "So am I right to feel as intense as I feel?", "question_tokens": ["So", "am", "I", "right", "to", "feel", "as", "intense", "as", "I", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "You know what, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "what", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "These are the kinds of shows that we're celebrating nowadays quite frankly and you're all surprised?", "question_tokens": ["These", "are", "the", "kinds", "of", "shows", "that", "we", "'re", "celebrating", "nowadays", "quite", "frankly", "and", "you", "'re", "all", "surprised", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "And let me ask you this Star.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "let", "me", "ask", "you", "this", "Star", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "Obviously what do you make to Barbara, what an extraordinary career she's had, isn't she?", "question_tokens": ["Obviously", "what", "do", "you", "make", "to", "Barbara", ",", "what", "an", "extraordinary", "career", "she", "'s", "had", ",", "is", "n't", "she", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "NNP", ",", "WP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "I have to tell you, I said many times I've had two great mentors in my career.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "to", "tell", "you", ",", "I", "said", "many", "times", "I", "'ve", "had", "two", "great", "mentors", "in", "my", "career", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barbara"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "What does that word mean to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "that", "word", "mean", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "That means a male.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "means", "a", "male", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "A black male?", "question_tokens": ["A", "black", "male", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "NN", ",", "JJ", "MD", "VB", "NNP", ",", "CC", "JJR", "CC", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "Black or white?", "question_tokens": ["Black", "or", "white", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "Black -- any kind, Chinese could say Nigga, but nigger or nigger.", "answer_tokens": ["Black", "--", "any", "kind", ",", "Chinese", "could", "say", "Nigga", ",", "but", "nigger", "or", "nigger", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "Because that's the racist word.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "that", "'s", "the", "racist", "word", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "Where have we ended up you think at the year after debating all of this?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "have", "we", "ended", "up", "you", "think", "at", "the", "year", "after", "debating", "all", "of", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "Right where we started.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "where", "we", "started", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "Can I just say something, Piers?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "just", "say", "something", ",", "Piers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "Yeah, exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "This guy is an extraordinary man in many ways, isn't he?", "question_tokens": ["This", "guy", "is", "an", "extraordinary", "man", "in", "many", "ways", ",", "is", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "Yeah, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "Yeah?", "question_tokens": ["Yeah", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "... to play the ukulele.", "answer_tokens": ["...", "to", "play", "the", "ukulele", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 565, "question": "That's it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 566, "answer": "That's the biggest muscle you've seen for a while.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "the", "biggest", "muscle", "you", "'ve", "seen", "for", "a", "while", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 573, "question": "Three?", "question_tokens": ["Three", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "aSentId": 574, "answer": "... but twice.", "answer_tokens": ["...", "but", "twice", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "Three?", "question_tokens": ["Three", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "Twice.", "answer_tokens": ["Twice", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 581, "question": "Did you have one?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "have", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "Literally at war with everyone?", "question_tokens": ["Literally", "at", "war", "with", "everyone", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Snoop Dogg", "Snoop"], "PERSON": ["Snoop"]}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "NNP", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 678, "question": "Away from the old Snoop to -- well from Dogg to Lion, what of you make of it?", "question_tokens": ["Away", "from", "the", "old", "Snoop", "to", "--", "well", "from", "Dogg", "to", "Lion", ",", "what", "of", "you", "make", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "TO", ":", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "NNP", ",", "WP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 679, "answer": "The funniest part about Snoop Dogg, Snoop Lion, Snoop anything he wants to call him so Snoop is Snoop.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "funniest", "part", "about", "Snoop", "Dogg", ",", "Snoop", "Lion", ",", "Snoop", "anything", "he", "wants", "to", "call", "him", "so", "Snoop", "is", "Snoop", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 705, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 706, "answer": "Hi.", "answer_tokens": ["Hi", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN"], "qSentId": 723, "question": "What's the answer?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "answer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 724, "answer": "Because he's a (inaudible)", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "he", "'s", "a", "(", "inaudible", ")"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 733, "question": "Nischelle?", "question_tokens": ["Nischelle", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 734, "answer": "Because he's fabulous.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "he", "'s", "fabulous", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 738, "question": "Can I go for bleep?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "go", "for", "bleep", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 739, "answer": "Don't do it.", "answer_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "do", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 836, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 837, "answer": "Yes, I mean, you know, she said the conversation is happening and the truth of the matter is the conversation sadly isn't even happening.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "you", "know", ",", "she", "said", "the", "conversation", "is", "happening", "and", "the", "truth", "of", "the", "matter", "is", "the", "conversation", "sadly", "is", "n't", "even", "happening", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 850, "question": "Now, what is going to change this?", "question_tokens": ["Now", ",", "what", "is", "going", "to", "change", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 851, "answer": "It's going to take people to have the courage and strength to stand up against a very powerful.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "going", "to", "take", "people", "to", "have", "the", "courage", "and", "strength", "to", "stand", "up", "against", "a", "very", "powerful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]